[{"answer": "I'm very good.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Candy, how are you?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "You must feel like you've been --", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "Do you sense you're amongst people who believe they can win?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Hi, Piers.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Clearly there's not that kind of huge euphoria we saw four years ago but that doesn't necessarily mean his vote won't come out and re-elect him, but are they confident or are they nervous?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Great, Piers.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "David, how are you?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting, Piers.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "Do you see that as perhaps the pivotal state?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I have been out with him for months in this campaign and I think he's bringing that fire and passion every day.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "He seems to have finally revved up but if it's too late, he's going to kick himself, isn't he?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, Rudy Giuliani, you know, might be the only person in America who believes that.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Fine, Piers.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "I think we have a real chance of winning this.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "When you look at the polls today, for example, there are so many of them but are there any that you've seen where you feel, OK, we've got a real chance of winning this?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "The truth hurts.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "I think the first debate obviously.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "If Mitt Romney wins the election, what do you think in the end will have been the key determining factor?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Do you feel slightly fortunate you're not the guy that has to try and beat him tomorrow?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Well, I think we have two parallel universes that are -- that are very, very different.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "When you see how things have all washed up now on the eve of the election, with your political historian hat on, where do you think we could be in for some shocks tomorrow specifically?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "I can't comment until we see the returns tomorrow night, just because you're asking me a question that we have to see how close it is, what the circumstances are.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "If Mitt Romney loses, and obviously it's very, very close, but if he does lose, I appreciate it's a hypothetical, where do you wish he had gone harder that may have guaranteed victory?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, Piers, you asked me about -- here's an alternative universe.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "I didn't have to do anything to remind anybody about the decision that Barack Obama made to pull the trigger on Osama bin Laden.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "I mean, you did this clearly to remind everybody as they're about to vote what a hero Barack Obama is, right?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "You know, I voted for George Pataki and I voted for Rudy Giuliani and I voted for Michael Bloomberg.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "I know you're an Obama supporter, but are you still a bit nervous that the vote may not come out tomorrow?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Piers, next year, you know, Mitt Romney will be unemployed, from what I'm looking at.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Rather than having all the heartthrobs around you?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Good to be with you.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "Governor, how are you?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "Well, all across the Midwest, it's incredibly important.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "And which one could be the turning point?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Well, it's definitely about turnout.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Is that really what you guys are relying on, his vote not turning out in that kind of degree?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I said it's good to talk to you.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "It could.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "Do you think it could all come down to Ohio tomorrow night?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Well, as far as Ohio is concerned, I think the president has had and has maintained, as I said, a consistent lead for a variety of reasons.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "How significant do you think it's been, Hurricane Sandy and the way that played out for both sides?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, these are different times, obviously.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "What is his great plan to get this country going?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Mitt Romney has bridged the gender gap.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "What went wrong in the last couple weeks?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I don't think any woman is looking forward to a Romney administration.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Are you looking forward to a Romney administration?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "He couldn't be more clear.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "If I was a woman, I'd be like, well, what do you believe?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Absolutely, it's offensive.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "I mean, Cecile, am I wrong about this, or does it just cause a lot of offense to women?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, let me make an important point.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Yes, I mean, Alice Stewart, final word to you, why would he want to get rid of Planned Parenthood?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "He's made it quite clear where he stands.", "docId": "121105pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Would you like to see Governor Romney overturning Roe v. Wade, or trying to if he became president?", "qSentId": 574}]